<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kirin recipe</string>
    <string name="welcome">Your recipe mix is up to you!</string>
    <string name="basic_information">Basic information</string>
    <string name="name_label">Name</string>
    <string name="Age_label">Age</string>
    <string name="Gender_label">Gender</string>
    <string name="name_hint"><![CDATA[First name & Last name]]></string>
    <string name="gender_hint">Choose your Gender here</string>
    <string name="height_label">Height</string>
    <string name="weight_label">Weight</string>
    <string name="age_hint">Your age</string>
    <string name="height_hint">Your height (cm)</string>
    <string name="weight_hint">Your weight (kg)</string>
    <string name="Preference_info">Preference</string>
    <string name="favorite_label">Favorite</string>
    <string name="favorite_hint">Choose your favorite type here</string>
    <string name="dislike_label">Dislike</string>
    <string name="Sign_out">Sign out</string>
    <string name="about_Setting">About us</string>
    <string name="contact_Setting">Pk with us</string>
    <string name="userinfo_Setting">Basic information</string>
    <string name="dislike_Setting">Dislike recipe</string>
    <string name="history_Setting">History record</string>
    <string name="search_recipe">Search</string>
    <string name="searchbar_diy"> Please enter the keywords</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="dislike_hint">Choose your dislike type here</string>
    <string-array name="recipe_type">
        <item>Choose your main recipe type here</item>
        <item>Seafood</item>
        <item>Pork</item>
        <item>Mutton</item>
        <item>Beef</item>
        <item>Poultry</item>
        <item>Vegetables</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="favorite_type">
        <item>Choose your favorite type here</item>
        <item>Seafood</item>
        <item>Pork</item>
        <item>Mutton</item>
        <item>Beef</item>
        <item>Poultry</item>
        <item>Vegetables</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dislike_type">
        <item>Choose your dislike type here</item>
        <item>Seafood</item>
        <item>Pork</item>
        <item>Mutton</item>
        <item>Beef</item>
        <item>Poultry</item>
        <item>Vegetables</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Gender_type">
        <item>Choose your Gender here</item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>None</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="stir_fried_pork_with_scallions">

Stir fried pork with scallions
        \nBeijing Cuisine
        \n
\nPer 100g - calories: 143 kcal
\nIngredients: 65g pork, 15g green Onions
\nSeasoning: 2g ginger, 4g garlic, 2g cooking wine, 4g soy sauce, 2g vinegar, 2g salt, 2g sugar, trace pepper, trace starch, 2g monosodium glutamate
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: In a mixing bowl, combine the meat, starch, cooking wine, pepper, and refined salt.
\n2: slice the green onion into small pieces.
\n3: heat a wok, pour in cooking oil, wait for the temperature of the oil to rise, then add the meat and stir-fry on high heat.
\n4: Cook until the ginger and garlic are fragrant.
\n5: Add the onion and stir-fry for a few minutes.
\n6: add the cooking wine, soy sauce, sugar, and salt, then the vinegar along the side of the pot, and finally the MSG.
    </string>
    <string name="lamb_soup">

Lamb soup
\n
\nPer 100 g - Calories: 62 kcal
\nIngredients: 90g lamb
\nSeasoning: cooking wine, 5g green onion, 2g ginger, pepper, dried orange peel, hawthorn, 3g salt
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Soak the lamb in cool water for two hours, changing the water at intervals of one hour.
\n2: Wash the lamb with water and cut it into small pieces.
\n3: Pour enough water into the pot, put the cut lamb pieces into the pot.
\n4: medium heat do open the pot and skim off the foam, pour in the cooking wine.
\n5: then add peppercorns, onion and ginger, dried orange peel and hawthorn.
\n6: cover the pot, turn low heat and slow stew 1-1.5 hours later.
\n7: the orange peel and hawthorn out, then sprinkle the appropriate amount of salt.
\n8: turn the medium heat and continue to stew for 15-20 minutes and then turn off the heat can be eaten.

    </string>

    <string name="cumin_lamb">
Cumin lamb
\n
\nPer 100g - Calories: 142 kcal
\nIngredients: 90g lamb
\nSeasoning: 5g soy sauce, tahini powder, 3g cumin granules, salt to taste, 2g cumin powder, chili powder, pepper powder, cooked white sesame seeds
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Soak the lamb in cool water for two hours, changing the water at intervals of one hour.
\n2: Wash the lamb with water and cut it into small pieces.
\n3: Pour enough water into the pot and put the cut lamb pieces into the pot.
\n4: medium heat do open the pot and skim off the foam, pour in the cooking wine.
\n5: then add peppercorns, onion and ginger, dried orange peel and hawthorn.
\n6: cover the pot, turn low heat and slow stew 1-1.5 hours later.
\n7: the orange peel and hawthorn out, then sprinkle the appropriate amount of salt.
\n8: turn the medium heat and continue to stew for 15-20 minutes and then turn off the heat can be eaten.
    </string>

    <string name="sauted_meat_shreds_with_soy_bean_paste">
Sauted meat shreds with soy bean paste
        \nBeijing Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 162 kcal
\nIngredients: 50g pork tenderloin, 10g green Onions, 10g bean slices, 10g cucumber
\nSeasoning: 5g sweet flour sauce, 3g white sugar, 2g sesame oil, 5g soy sauce, trace cooking wine, 5g egg white, trace starch, trace scallion ginger water
\n
\nSteps:
        \n1: cut pork tenderloin into thin shreds.
\n2: add salt, soy sauce, pepper, cooking wine, cooking oil, mix well and marinate for 20 minutes.
\n3: Place the bean skin in boiling water for 3 minutes and set aside.
\n4: cut the white onion into thin shreds and the cucumber into strips; set aside.
\n5: pour the sweet noodle sauce into a mixing bowl and stir in the sugar, sesame oil, green onion, and ginger water.
\n6: marinated shredded meat, egg white, starch, and thoroughly mixed.
\n7: heat a small amount of oil in a pan over medium heat, pour in the marinated meat, quickly scraped, and stir-fried until the meat shreds brown Sheng.
\n8: in the pan with the remaining oil, pour in the sweet noodle sauce and stir well.
\n9: stir-fry thoroughly, then add the shredded meat stir-fry.
\n10: to evenly coat all shredded meat with sauce.
    </string>
    <string name="grilled_eggplant">
Grilled eggplant
        \nBeijing Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 65 kcal
Ingredients: 60g eggplant, 10g meat slices, 5g carrot slices, 5g green pepper segments
\nSeasoning: 5g green Onions, 5g garlic
\n
\nSteps:
        \n1: Peel the eggplant, cut it into hobble pieces, and wet the surface.
\n2: sprinkle dry starch on top, then turn the eggplant pieces in the pot to distribute the starch evenly.
\n3: Sprinkle dry starch on the eggplant pieces again, making the eggplant wet, turn the eggplant pieces in the pot, and make the starch hang evenly on the eggplant.
\n4: pour the oil into the pot, and heat the oil to make bubbles around the eggplant block.
\n5: cook all of the eggplant pieces over medium heat.
\n6: if the surface of the eggplant block is hard, you can fish it out.
\n7: frying pan , heat the oil to about 80% of its original temperature, then add all of the eggplant pieces and re-fry until the eggplant is cooked. Control the oil by removing it from it.
\n8: Heat a small amount of oil in a separate pan and stir in the minced garlic. Stir in the sliced meat, carrots, and green pepper.
\n9: Pour the sauce into the pan and stir until the gravy is transparent.
\n10: Pour the fried eggplant pieces into the gravy, sprinkle with shredded green onion, quickly stir-fry, and allow the gravy to hang evenly on the eggplant.
\n11: Remove from the pan and drizzle with oil.
    </string>
    <string name="fish_head_with_minced_pepper">
Fish Head with Minced Pepper
\nHunan Cuisine
        \n
\nPer 100g - calories: 113 kcal
\nIngredients: 70g fish head, 5g green onion, 2g ginger, 3g garlic, 10g chopped chilli
\nSeasoning: 5g salt, a little pepper, 5g chicken essence
\n
        \nSteps:
\n1: Scrub fish head with salt, rinse off brine, and rub evenly with one teaspoon pepper, half tablespoon cooking oil, half teaspoon salt, and half teaspoon chicken seasoning.
\n2: bottom onion, ginger, and garlic
\n3: steam chopped pepper for 8 minutes on a false fire for 2 minutes.
\n4: add minced onion, ginger, and garlic.
\n5: heat the oil and pour it over the fish when it begins to smoke.
    </string>

    <string name="granny_smith">
Granny smith
\nHunan Cuisine
        \n
\nPer 100g - calories: 89 kcal
\nIngredients: 50g dried plum vegetables, 10g pork belly, 5g peanuts, 5g rice, 10g red pepper, 5g green onion, 5g garlic shoots
\nSeasoning: 3g light soy sauce, a little pepper, a little salt, 3g chicken essence, 4g green pepper
\n
        \nSteps:
\n1: dried plum cabbage warm water soak half an hour.
\n2: prepare the side dishes.
\n3: chopped chili pepper, onion, and ginger are cut; garlic seedlings are chopped.
\n4: Streaky Pork is frozen and cut into small dice.
\n5: cook the peanut rice in the microwave oven, peel it, and then fry it in a frying pan to make it crisper.
\n6: heat the oil in a pot, then brown the onion and ginger, then stir-fry the pancetta, add soy sauce and a little soy sauce for color, stir-fry the dried plum vegetables, add a small spoonful of water, stir-fry the chili peppers, then add garlic, salt, chicken essence, pepper, and pour in the peanut rice.
    </string>

    <string name="roast_duck">
JinLin Roast Duck
\nSu Cuisine
        \n
\nPer 100g - calories: 265 kcal
\nIngredients: 80g duck, 10g potato
\nSeasoning: 5g soy sauce, a little cayenne pepper, 2g ginger, 3g maltose, a little ground Chinese pepper, cinnamon, star anise, a little cooking wine, a little salt
\n
\nSteps:
        \n1: Wash the duck, control the water, rub it all over with salt, then add soy sauce, cooking wine, star anise, cinnamon, pepper powder, chili powder, ginger, mix these seasonings well, marinate the duck in it, place it in a plastic bag, place it in the refrigerator, and marinate it overnight.
\n2: The marinated duck will be removed the next day and placed in a cool place to dry naturally.
\n3: Next, dilute the maltose with a little water and brush the duck all over with a brush, making sure to coat all of the duck
\n4: Line a baking dish with tin foil and place the potato slices in it.
\n5: bake for 1 hour on the lower middle layer in a preheated 160 degree oven, after 30 minutes remove and brush once with maltose water, and wrap the wings and joints in tinfoil, after 1 hour turn the oven down to 200 degrees and bake for about 15 minutes.

    </string>

    <string name="braised_pork_balls_in_gravy">
Braised pork balls in gravy
\nSu Cuisine
        \n
\nPer 100g - calories: 261 kcal
\nIngredients: 60g pork, 10g quail eggs, 10g horseshoe, 10g bread bran
\nIngredients: 5g light soy sauce, 1g dark soy sauce, 3g rock sugar, 1g yellow rice wine, a dash of cinnamon, a dash of fragrant leaves
\n
\nSteps:
        \n1: prepare the ingredients.
\n2: quail eggs cleaned in water, cooked in a pot, over cold water shelled.
\n3: beat the meat into puree.
\n4: peel and chop the horse feet.
\n5: put the meat in a basin, add the eggs, chopped green onion, ground horseshoe, bread crumbs, soy sauce, salt, yellow wine.
\n6: along with the same side of the stirring on the strength.
\n7: put on disposable gloves, put the right amount of meat filling in your hands, and then put quail eggs, make the shape of meatballs, and then left and right hands back and forth to beat the meatballs a few times, so that the air is discharged, a little stronger.
\n8: pour the appropriate amount of oil into the pot, heat to 80% hot, add the meatballs.
\n9: deep-fried until the appearance of golden brown (oil should be higher temperature, meatballs under the frying pan to quickly set, not easy to fall apart).
\n10: pour out the oil in the pan, add fried meatballs, water, soy sauce, soy sauce, rock sugar, brown wine, cinnamon, allspice, chili, star anise, salt, high heat boil.
\n11: turn the small fire for about 30 minutes.

    </string>

    <string name="chinese_yam_in_hot_toffee">
Chinese Yam in Hot Toffee
\nShandong Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 321 kcal
\nIngredients: 60g yam, 15g soft white sugar, 10g cornstarch, vegetable oil
\nSeasoning: 3g light soy sauce, 2g dark soy sauce, 10g rock sugar, a little rice wine, a little cinnamon, a little bay leaf
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Peel and cut yam into hobnail pieces. (It is best to bring disposable gloves to prevent mucus irritation skin allergies).
\n2: soak yam pieces with clean water, drain.
\n3: pat on a little raw flour.
\n4: the pot on the fire with an appropriate amount of oil to 70% heat, one by one into the yam pieces.
\n5: deep-fried until crisp and hard, drain the oil.
\n6: grease the pan with a little oil to prevent sticking.
\n7: use another pot to add vegetable oil, sugar, the ratio of 1:3.
\n8: stirring constantly over low heat.
\n9: wait for the sugar to dissolve, continue to stir.
\n10: when the syrup becomes thin, light yellow color. (Must not be high temperature)
\n11: quickly put the fried yam pieces.
\n12: turn off the fire stirring evenly.

    </string>

    <string name="creamy_chinese_cabbage_in_soup">
Creamy Chinese Cabbage in Soup
\nShandong Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 97 kcal
\nIngredients: 30g cabbage, 10g shrimp skin, 30g water tofu, 20g milk powder
\nSeasoning: 3g garlic paste, 2g ginger slices, 5g cooked corn kernels, a little salt
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Soften the shrimp skin in warm water.
\n2: softened shrimp skin cut into minced. To be used.
\n3: cabbage cut into cubes, water tofu cut into cubes.
\n4: garlic cloves and ginger cubes are cut into minced and sliced.
\n5: milk powder melted with warm water, set aside.
\n6: the appropriate amount of cooked corn kernels.
\n7: Heat oil in a frying pan, add garlic and ginger, shrimp skin, stir-fry.
\n8: put cabbage pieces stir-fried for 2 minutes.
\n9: put in the seasoned powdered milk.
\n10: boil and into the water tofu block.

    </string>

    <string name="braised_eggplant">
Braised Eggplant
\nShandong Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 69 kcal
\nIngredients: 75g eggplant, 5g green pepper, 5g tomato
\nSeasoning: 3g garlic, 2g salt, 5g sugar, 10g peanut oil
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: wash and cut the eggplant into cubes and sprinkle some salt evenly and marinate for 10-20 minutes.
\n2: peppers and tomatoes cleaned and cut into pieces.
\n3: garlic some part sliced, part chopped.
\n4: the marinated eggplant will be clenched hard water, so that the eggplant can absorb less oil.
\n5: the pan is hot, put an appropriate amount of peanut oil, then put garlic cloves bursting.
\n6: smell the garlic aroma and add the eggplant, stir-fry over medium heat until the eggplant is browned and soft.
\n7: put the green pepper and tomatoes, add a spoonful of sugar and salt to taste, stir-fry evenly over high heat, add a little hot water halfway through the stir-fry to make the tomatoes soft and red soup.
\n8: sprinkle with chopped garlic before serving.

    </string>

    <string name="braised_beef_brisket">
Braised beef brisket
\nSichuan Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 232 kcal
\nIngredients: 50g sirloin, 5g ginger, 5g garlic, 20g potato, 10g carrot
\nSeasoning: a little star anise, 5g rock sugar, 3g Haitian seafood sauce, 2g light soy sauce, a little rice wine
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Cut the beef brisket into 40mmX40mm square pieces.
\n2: Boil water in a pot, add the brisket and cook until the water boils, remove and rinse.
\n3: Heat 1 tbsp oil in a pot, add rock sugar and cook slowly over low heat until it melts and turns caramel color.
\n4: Add ginger, green onion and star anise and stir-fry until fragrant.
\n5: Add beef brisket and stir-fry until evenly colored.
\n6: Add rice wine, seafood sauce, stir-fry until evenly colored.
\n7: Inject of water, soy sauce, the water is higher than the meat, high heat boil and simmer for 90 minutes.
\n8: Heat 1 tbsp oil in a separate pan and sauté the carrots and potatoes until light brown on the surface.
\n9: Add the beef brisket and the stock to the pot. Bring to a boil and continue to simmer for about 60 minutes.


    </string>

    <string name="wenchang_coconut_chicken">
Wenchang Coconut Chicken
\nYue Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 144 kcal
\nIngredients: 80g chicken thigh meat, 5g spring onion , 5g ginger , 5g garlic
\nSeasoning: 3g soy sauce, 2g sugar, a little sesame oil, a little vinegar
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Wash the chicken thighs, scald them with hot water first, then boil them in water, put green onion and ginger in the water and cook them at the same time.
\n2: Chicken thighs cooked and cooled, chopped into small pieces and placed in a plate.
\n3: Chop all the onion, ginger, garlic and chili, sauté in oil and add all the seasonings and cook well, serve and pour over the chicken thighs.


    </string>

    <string name="dongpo_pork">
DongPo Pork
\nSZhe Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 463 kcal
\nIngredients: 80g pork pancetta
\nSeasoning: small amount of star anise, 5g rock sugar, small amount of yellow wine, 5g soy sauce, 5g shallots, 5g green onions, small amount of ginger
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Wash the pork first.
\n2: Boil in a pot of boiling water for about 8 minutes.
\n3: Remove and cool, then cut into 3cm cubes.
\n4: Bottom of the pot with a few pieces of bamboo chopsticks built into the bottom of the well, arrange the scallions.
\n5: Put ginger slices, place the meat pieces skin side down, nearly the amount of the dense arrangement of the best stuffed.
\n6: Add soy sauce and fresh soy sauce, pour on the old yellow wine, put on the rock sugar, high heat boil to low heat and slow stew 2 hours.
\n7: Take out the skin side up into a container with a lid, steam for 1 hour on high heat to remove.
\n8: Boil the soup when stewing meat, add water starch thickening, pour on the steamed meat.


    </string>

    <string name="stir_fried_pork_with_green_peppers">
Stir fried pork with green peppers
\nSichuan Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 101 kcal
\nIngredients: 30g green pepper, 60g pork
\nSeasoning: 5g soy sauce, 2g sesame oil, chicken broth, cornstarch, sesame seeds, 3g salt, ginger, garlic, soy sauce, cooking wine, pepper, sugar
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Wash and cut green pepper into 3 cm long julienne strips and marinate in salt for a few minutes.
\n2: Wash the pork, cut into 3 cm long, 5 mm wide and 5 mm thick shreds, mix with salt and 40 g of cornstarch and marinate for a while.
\n3: Put soy sauce and 35g starch into a bowl and thicken with chicken broth to make gravy.
\n4: Heat a frying pan, add oil and heat to 70%, pour in the peppers, stir-fry over high heat and remove.
\n5: Add 25 grams of sesame oil, heat, add the shredded meat, stir-fry a few times, pour in the shredded peppers, add a small amount of cornstarch, stir-fry a few times, sprinkle with roasted sesame seeds, ready.


    </string>

    <string name="poached_young_chinese_cabbage">
Poached young Chinese cabbage
\nSichuan Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 11 kcal
\nIngredients: 90g Cantonese cabbage
\nSeasoning: 5g salt, 3g chicken essence, a small amount of starch, 1g green onion, 1g red pepper
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Boil half a pot of water, add a small amount of salt and oil, into the cabbage heart cook for about 1 minutes.
\n2: Put the boiled cabbage heart neatly on the plate, cut the red pepper and green onion into shreds and use.
\n3: Heat the oil in the wok, add oyster sauce and umami juice, add shredded red pepper and stock, boil until slightly boiling, add a little starch.
\n4: Put shredded red pepper and scallion on the cabbage, and drizzle the soup on the cabbage.


    </string>

    <string name="steamed_yellow_croaker">
Steamed Yellow Croaker
\nYue Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 209 kcal
\nIngredients: Yellowtail 90g
\nSeasoning: ginger, onion 3g, steamed fish soya sauce 5g,, salt 2g
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Ginger cut half into slices, half cut into shreds, white onion cut sections, cut the leaves of the electrum not. The bottom of the plate lay onion and ginger slices
\n2: Yellow croaker collection hitch open, split open, the fish body smeared with a thin layer of salt marinated for 10 minutes, laid on the plate, the fish and then placed on the cut ginger shreds.
\n3: The pot of water boiling and put the marinated fish into the pot, steam for seven minutes on high heat.
\n4: Out of the pot and pour off the water steamed out of the dish.
\n5: Two tablespoons of steamed fish soy sauce.
\n6: Sprinkle with chopped green onion.
\n7: Another pot to heat up two spoons of cooking oil drizzled on the fish.


    </string>

    <string name="char_siu">
BBQ Pork with Honey Sauce
\nYue Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 206 kcal
\nIngredients: 90g pork belly
\nSeasoning: 3g char siu sauce, 3g oyster sauce, 2g light soy sauce, shredded ginger, 2g honey
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: After peeling and washing the pork belly, cut two sections.
\n2: Place in a clean, dry crisper and sprinkle with shredded ginger.
\n3: Pour in 2 tablespoons of char siu sauce, 1 tablespoon of light soy sauce and 1 tablespoon of oil.
\n4: After mixing, cover and refrigerate for two days. During this period, the meat should be turned many times to fully taste the meat.
\n5: After two days, remove the meat from the refrigerator and defrost for half an hour.
\n6: Preheat the oven at 190°, line a non-stick baking tray with tinfoil, put the meat and a little juice on it and send it to the middle oven for 30 minutes.
\n7: 5 minutes to turn once, 10 minutes after the start of the honey, brush a layer of honey before the oven.
\n8: When the temperature drops slightly after coming out of the oven, start slicing.


    </string>

    <string name="hakka_stuffed_tofu">
Hakka stuffed tofu
\n Yue Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 89 kcal
\nIngredients: 50g tofu, 20g minced pork, 20g egg
\nSeasoning: chopped cilantro, scallion, starch, 3g sugar, 3g salt, chopped pepper, 2g oyster sauce, 2g soy sauce
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Add chopped green onion, egg mixture, salt and soy sauce to the minced pork and mix well.
\n2: Cut the triangle of oil tofu in half, hollow out the middle, stuff it with the stirred minced pork and smooth it out.
\n3: Wrap the oiled tofu stuffed with meat into a pot of cold water and cook
\n4: Mix the seasoning with minced cilantro, chopped pepper, oyster sauce, sugar and appropriate amount of water, and add a little of the water used to cook the oil tofu to thicken it, pour it into the pot and cook together.


    </string>

    <string name="sweet_and_sour_pork_tenderloin">
Sweet and Sour Pork Tenderloin
\n Yue Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 267 kcal
\nIngredients: 65g minced pork, 20g egg
\nSeasoning: 5g tomato sauce, scallion, starch, 5g sugar, salt, chopped pepper, 3g oyster sauce, 2g soy sauce
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Fresh tenderloin meat cut into long strips. Marinate the meat with salt and wine, then coat with egg white and cornstarch.
\n2: Pour Spanish olive oil into the pan, wait until the oil is 6 mature, then add the meat and fry it until it is fifty percent dry.
\n3: Pan oil left to pop garlic and pepper, add shallots, tomato sauce and sauté well.
\n4: Pour into the meat and stir-fry, put vinegar, thicken, plate.

    </string>

    <string name="ma_po_tofu">
Ma Po Tofu
\n Sichuan Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories:  119 kcal
\nIngredients: 60g tofu, 25g ground beef
\nSeasoning: 3g minced green garlic, 3g minced ginger and garlic, edible oil, salt, 3g soy sauce, 5g red oil bean paste, bean drum, cayenne pepper powder, 1g chicken essence, cooking wine
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Prepare the materials, beef chopped into minced in advance.
\n2: Beef with salt, soy sauce, cooking wine stir well marinated for 10 minutes.
\n3: Tofu cut into pieces, let go of water blanching, boil water and cook for 5 minutes.
\n4: Hot pan with cool oil, add ginger and garlic stir-fried aroma and add beef stir-fried until browned.
\n5: Add chopped bean drums, red oil bean paste, chili powder stir-fry well.
\n6: Add a small amount of water and then add blanched tofu and simmer for ten minutes.
\n7: Add pepper powder, chicken seasoning stir-fry well, add some water starch and stir well, then plate, sprinkle with minced green garlic.


    </string>

    <string name="double_cooked_pork">
Double cooked pork
\n Sichuan Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 315 kcal
\nIngredients: 60g pork belly, 10g green pepper, 10g green garlic, 10g red pepper
\nSeasoning: 5g Pixian thick broad-bean sauce, 2g black bean sauce, 3g white sugar, chicken essence, peanut oil
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Cold water under the meat, boil over high heat, cook until the meat is just cooked, and then cut into thin slices after the meat is cool.
\n2: Cold water under the meat, boil over high heat, cook until the meat is just cooked (with chopsticks can penetrate without seeping blood), and then cut into thin slices after the meat cools.
\n3: Frying pan, stir-fry the meat slices.
\n4: To be a little volume of meat out of the oil, under the PI County bean paste stir-fry well.
\n5: Then add the chopped tempeh stir-fry.
\n6: Add green and red pepper, stir-fry until broken green.
\n7: Add the green garlic stir-fried aroma.
\n8: Finally, then add sugar, chicken seasoning can be removed from the pot.


    </string>

    <string name="kung_pao_chicken">
Braised beef brisket
\n Sichuan Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 268 kcal
\nIngredients: 70g chicken breast, 10g green onion, 10g fried peanuts, a few pieces of chili pepper
\nSeasoning: 2g salt, 3g soy sauce, 1g dark soy sauce, balsamic vinegar, 3g sugar, ginger juice, garlic paste, 2g chicken seasoning, pepper powder, white pepper, cooking wine
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Pat the chicken breast with the back of a knife and cut into thumbnail-sized dice.
\n2: Marinate with 1 tablespoon cooking wine, ½ tablespoon cooking oil, ½ teaspoon white pepper, ½ teaspoon salt and 1 teaspoon cornstarch for 10 minutes to taste.
\n3: Cut green onion into pieces.
\n4: Heat oil in a pot and stir-fry the diced chicken at 70% to 80% heat.
\n5: Add dried chili, green onion and a teaspoon of pepper and stir-fry to bring out the fragrance.
\n6: Blend into the sauce, high heat stir-fry until sticky dry loose.
\n7: Turn off the heat, mix in the peanut rice.


    </string>

    <string name="sliced_beef_and_ox_tongue_in_chilli_sauce">
Sliced Beef and Ox Tongue in Chilli Sauce
\n Sichuan Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 138 kcal
\nIngredients: 20g beef tendon, 20g beef tripe, 10g beef tongue, 10g beef tendon, 10g beef heart, 5g sesame seeds, 5g peanuts without skin
\nSeasoning: 5g chili powder, crushed chili pepper, pepper, cloves, cinnamon, cumin, herb nuts, star anise, allspice, ginger, 5g green onion, comfrey, salad oil, 5g soy sauce, soy sauce, rock sugar, 5g brown sugar
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Boiling red oil preparation materials: chili powder 4/3 cup, chili pepper 1/4 cup (1 cup = 250 ml the same below), pepper 1 tablespoon, cloves 3, cinnamon half a small strip, cumin 1 small spoon, herb nuts 1, star anise 4, allspice 3 pieces, ginger 1 small piece, green onion 3 sections, sesame 1 tablespoon, comfrey 1 small section. Add 200 grams of peanuts without skin and 600 grams of salad oil (or vegetable oil).
\n2: Oil poured into the pan, oil temperature slightly hot add peanuts, fry over moderate heat until slightly yellow and crispy.
\n3: Fish out, part can be used as ingredients.
\n4: Add the other ingredients listed above (except sesame seeds) to the frying pan and immediately turn to the lowest heat. Simmer for 1 hour, then add sesame seeds and simmer for another 15 minutes.
\n5: Pour all the ingredients in the frying pan into a bowl.
\n6: After soaking for 1 day, remove the residue and drain out the red oil. Save for multiple use.
\n7: Boil soy sauce preparation materials: 1 cup of soy sauce, 3 tablespoons of soy sauce, 1 small piece of rock sugar, 3 tablespoons of brown sugar, peppercorns, star anise, cumin, allspice, ginger, scallions. All the above ingredients are shown in the picture.
\n8: All the ingredients into the pot, boil and turn to simmer for 30 minutes.
\n9: Strain out the residue.
\n10: Soy sauce into a container to save, can be used many times.
\n11: The third step: cooking beef and modulating red oil sauce water not over the beef, add the right amount of cooking wine, salt, star anise, green onions and ginger will be cooked until slightly rotten. Can be difficult to cook parts such as tendons, tendons, etc. cooked in a pressure cooker.
\n12: Cooked beef miscellaneous removed and cooled, cut into thin slices and placed in a bowl of some depth.
\n13: Prepare stock, season with salt and chicken seasoning (I used clear chicken stock already has a taste.
\n14: Make red oil sauce: the ratio is about: red oil half a cup, half a cup of stock, boiled soy sauce 3 tablespoons, pepper powder half a small spoon, sesame oil 1 tablespoon, salt half a small spoon.
\n15: The seasoned red oil sauce poured on the beef (the amount of red oil sauce to grasp the amount of beef can be soaked in it), plus chopped green onions, cilantro and fried peanuts.



    </string>

    <string name="west_lake_fried_fish_in_vinegar">
West Lake fried fish in vinegar
\n Zhe Cuisine
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 122 kcal
\nIngredients: 80g grass carp
\nSeasoning: Chili powder, crushed chili pepper, Sichuan peppercorns, cloves, cinnamon, cumin, grass nuts, star anise, sesame leaves, 5g ginger, 5g shallot, comgrass, salad oil, 3g soy sauce, 3g dark soy sauce, 3g rock sugar, 1g brown sugar
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: First cut the spring onion into sections, ginger slice and set aside.
\n2: Wash the fish with boiling water, scrape the mucus of the fish body with a knife, and then break the fish with a knife, and cut the flower knife on the fish body.
\n3: Pour water into the pot, add scallion segments and ginger slices, and season with rice wine, salt, pepper and monosodium glutamate.
\n4: The water is boiling down into the fish, when the water is boiling again switch the fire.
\n5: Turn off the heat, cover the pot and stew for 5 minutes.
\n6: At this time, heat another pot, add a little oil to stir stir ginger, then cook into the rice wine, pour 150ml fish soup.
\n7: Add 50 grams of balsamic vinegar, 2 tablespoons of sugar about 40 grams, and 2 grams of salt.
\n8: When the soup is boiling, thicken with starch.
\n9: Drizzle with sweet and sour sauce and serve.


    </string>

    <string name="braised_chicken_with_scallion">
Braised beef brisket
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 145 kcal
\nIngredients: 70g chicken, 10g spring onion, 5g ginger, 5g garlic, millet pepper
\nSeasoning: Oil, cooking wine, 5g light soy sauce, 2g dark soy sauce, 3g salt, five-spice powder, black pepper
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: After the chicken is washed, use 2 tablespoons of five-spice powder and 2 tablespoons of salt and an appropriate amount of black pepper, marinate it, prick a few holes and massage to help taste, wrap it with plastic wrap and leave it for half an hour. Cut the scallions into sections and cut the ginger into thick slices.
\n2: Take a small bowl, add 3 spoons of cooking wine and 2 spoons of light soy sauce, stir well, cover the pot with oil and ginger, anti-stick spread on the green onion segment, put the cured chicken on the sauce just mixed.
\n3: Do not add water, after the fire boils, turn the heat to simmer 20 minutes to open the lid, put some scallion on the chicken add two spoons of light soy sauce, a spoon of dark soy sauce, color evenly.
\n4: Cover the pot and simmer for 10-15 minutes.


    </string>

    <string name="egg_seaweed_soup">
Egg Seaweed Soup
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 36 kcal
\nIngredients: 50g nori, 30g egg, 10g shrimp
\nSeasoning: 5g scallion, sesame oil, 3g monosodium glutamate, 2g salt
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Wash and shred the seaweed and put it into a bowl. Add two-thirds of the shrimps.
\n2: Put the right amount of water in the pot to boil, and then pour into the mixed egg liquid.
\n3: Such as frangipani float, add salt, MSG and then pour the soup into the seaweed bowl, drizzle 2, 3 drops of sesame oil, and finally sprinkle with green onion.


    </string>

    <string name="lamb_stew_with_carrots">
Lamb stew with carrots
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 144 kcal
\nIngredients: 30g carrot, 60g lamb
\nSeasoning: cooking wine, 2g green onion, 2g ginger, 2g garlic, 2g sugar, 2g salt, sesame oil
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Wash and drain the carrots and lamb, and cut the carrots and lamb into pieces.
\n2: Put the lamb into boiling water and blanch, then drain.
\n3: Put the lamb in a frying pan, add the salad oil and stir-fry the lamb over high heat until the color turns white.
\n4: Add carrots, water and other seasonings (except sesame oil) into the pot and bring to a boil over high heat.


    </string>

    <string name="beef_brisket_with_tomatoes_in_casserole_beef">
Beef Brisket with Tomatoes in Casserole Beef
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 141 kcal
\nIngredients: 50g beef brisket, 30g tomato, 10g onion
\nSeasoning:  ginger, 5g tomato sauce, 5g soy sauce, cooking wine, salt
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Pot of water on the boil, blanch the brisket.
\n2: Tomatoes cut small dice, onions cut small dice spare.
\n3: Heat the oil in a casserole dish under the ginger.
\n4: Stir-fry the onion.
\n5: Under the tomatoes stir-fry.
\n6: The tomatoes stir-fried until rotten soft state.
\n7: Add water to boil.
\n8: Add beef brisket.
\n9: Add the appropriate amount of tomato sauce, wine and soy sauce turn low heat and stew for about 1 hour. Use chopsticks to hold the lid on the pot to prevent overflow.
\n10: Brisket stewed with a little salt to taste and then stew for about 20 minutes.

    </string>

    <string name="scalded_prawns">
Scalded prawns
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 107 kcal
\nIngredients: 85g shrimp
\nSeasoning: ginger, 5g garlic, rice wine, 3g salt, 5g seafood soy sauce, 2g sesame oil
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Shrimp washed and prepared with a toothpick to remove the shrimp thread.
\n2: Ginger slices, 2 cloves of garlic pat flat, another 2 cloves of garlic chopped into garlic drizzle seafood soy sauce ready.
\n3: Pot of water, add the ginger, garlic and salt, and then drizzle in the rice wine.
\n4: Boil and add shrimp.
\n5: The shrimp body curled red immediately off the heat, simmer in water for 1 minute, take out the shrimp and put on a plate.
\n6: Add oil to another pot.
\n7: Sesame oil is hot, drizzle over the garlic soy sauce.


    </string>

    <string name="pineapple_with_shrimp_balls">
Pineapple with Shrimp Balls
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 128 kcal
\nIngredients: 20g pineapple, 50g shrimp, 10g green bell pepper, 10g red bell pepper
\nSeasoning: salt, 3g sugar, vinegar, cooking wine, 2g soy sauce, 5g tomato sauce, white pepper
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Shrimp shelled to remove the shrimp line open behind, with the right amount of salt, cooking wine, white pepper marinade 10 minutes, and then add the right amount of raw flour.
\n2: Pineapple cut in half to take the pulp and cut small pieces.
\n3: The other half of the pineapple with a spoon hollow to make a plate.
\n4: Red bell pepper and green bell pepper cut into small pieces.
\n5: Add oil to the pan, oil temperature of about 150 degrees, add shrimp, shrimp become red curl about 40 seconds to fish out.
\n6: The pan is hot, pour in the oil, pour in the pre-mixed sauce (with the right amount of white vinegar, sugar, salt, tomato paste), first put the bell pepper, then put the pineapple. Finally pour in the shrimp balls, stir-fry so that the ingredients are covered with sauce can be served.


    </string>


    <string name="steamed_egg_with_shrimp">
Steamed Egg with Shrimp
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 152 kcal
\nIngredients: 50g egg, 40g live shrimp
\nSeasoning: 2g green onion, ginger, 3g salt, cooking wine, 5g soy sauce
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Prepare the eggs, live shrimp, scallions and ginger.
\n2: Shrimp washed, head, shelled and diced into small pieces, add white onion and ginger, add wine, grasp and marinate for a few moments.
\n3: Knock the eggs into a bowl, add 1.5 to 2 times the warm water, add salt, stir well.
\n4: Strain with a slotted spoon into the bowl used for steaming.
\n5: Cover the bowl with plastic wrap, place it on a steamer rack and place it under cold water.
\n6: Cover and steam for about 5 minutes, until the egg mixture is solidified on the surface.
\n7: Open the plastic wrap and add the diced shrimp more evenly, then cover with plastic wrap again.
\n8: Cover and continue steaming until cooked through.

    </string>

    <string name="roast_beef_with_potatoes">
Roast Beef with Potatoes
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 265 kcal
\nIngredients: 60g beef, 20g potatoes, 10g carrots
\nSeasoning: chili, green onion, ginger, star anise, 3g rock sugar, 3g soy sauce, 1g cooking wine, oil, 3g salt
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Wash the beef, cut small pieces.
\n2: Carrots, potatoes peeled, cut hobble block.
\n3: Wash the onion and ginger, sliced, dried chili, star anise ready.
\n4: Put the right amount of water in the pot, put the beef pieces, blanching until the beef is browned, fish out.
\n5: Put an appropriate amount of oil in the pot, low heat, add rock sugar, stir-fry until the sugar melts and bubbles.
\n6: Add beef stir-fry, stir-fry until the beef is colored.
\n7: Add onion, ginger, chili, star anise, stir-fry, add a little soy sauce and cooking wine.
\n8: Stir-fry evenly, add the right amount of water, boil, add potatoes and carrots, put the right amount of salt to taste.
\n9: Stew over medium-low heat until the potatoes are soft and the soup is reduced, remove from the pot.


    </string>

    <string name="cumin_beef">
Cumin Beef
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 134 kcal
\nIngredients: 85g beef
\nSeasoning: 5g scallion, 1g ginger, 1g cooked sesame seeds, pepper, cumin, dried chili, oil, 1g sesame oil, 1g red oil, stock, 1g cooking wine, chili powder, five spice powder, 3g refined salt, 2g sugar, monosodium glutamate
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Wash and finely chop the onion and ginger.
\n2: Wash and de-tendonize the beef, rinse the blood and then slice it into thin slices and marinate it with salt, cooking wine, ginger and green onion for 15 minutes.
\n3: Fill the pot with cooking oil, heat to 50% heat, pour in the beef slices, fry until crisp and fragrant, then remove.
\n4: Reserve the oil in the pot, add dried chillies and peppers and stir-fry until fragrant, then add the sliced beef and stir-fry well.
\n5: Add stock, wine, five spice powder, sugar, boil and then add chili powder, cumin and stir-fry.
\n6: Add red oil, monosodium glutamate, sesame oil, stir-fry evenly, plate, sprinkle with sesame seeds.

    </string>

    <string name="stir_fried_beef_river_beef">
Stir-Fried Rice Noodles with Beef
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 148 kcal
\nIngredients: 40g river noodles, 30g beef tenderloin, 10g onion, 10g bean sprouts
\nSeasoning: 2g green onion, corn starch, cooking wine, 3g soy sauce, 3g oyster sauce, 1g salt, 1g pepper
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Onion shredded, onion cut into sections, bean sprouts remove the head and tail.
\n2: Beef tenderloin reverse shredded into slices, add a little soy sauce, salt, cooking wine, dry starch and vegetable oil, mix well and marinate for 15 minutes.
\n3: Heat a frying pan, add oil to heat and then put the beef slices quickly stir-fried, browned and served.
\n4: Another pot of hot oil, add the scattered river noodles, carefully stir-fried.
\n5: Add shredded onion seasoned with oyster sauce soy sauce pepper stir-fry well.
\n6: Add bean sprouts, scallions and beef slices stir-fried a few times.


    </string>

    <string name="moroccan_lamb_stew">
Moroccan Lamb Stew
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 133 kcal
\nIngredients: 60g lamb, 10g potatoes, 5g purple onion, 5g chervil, parsley, 5g carrots, 5g tomatoes
\nSeasoning: cloves, cinnamon, olive oil, 2g honey, 2g tomato paste, 2g butter, 2g cumin, 2g curry powder, black pepper, paprika
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: First cut the onion, potato, carrot, tomato and celery.
\n2: Debone the hindquarters and cut them into small pieces.
\n3: Put cumin, salt, chili powder, black pepper, olive oil, mix it well and marinate for half an hour.
\n4: Pour the marinated lamb into the pan and set aside when the surface is browned.
\n5: Put the butter into the pan and let it melt.
\n6: Pour the ingredients prepared before into the pan and stir-fry.


    </string>

    <string name="lamb_dumplings">
Lamb Dumplings
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 167 kcal
\nIngredients: 50g lamb, 20g carrot
\nSeasoning: 1g green onion, 1g ginger, 2g soy sauce, 20g flour, 2g pepper noodles, water, 2g oil, 2g salt
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Chopped green onion and ginger, put into the meat filling, sprinkle a little pepper noodles, add soy sauce marinade.
\n2: Rub carrot into shreds, chopped, put into the meat filling.
\n3: Add the right amount of oil and stir well, and finally add the right amount of salt.
\n4: Add 2 1/2 cups of flour and water, stir into snowflake shape, knead into dough and let it mellow for 15 minutes.
\n5: Molten dough, divided into small dough, rolled into dumplings.
\n6: Boil water in a pot, put in the dumplings, beat the water 3 times, dumplings cooked, fish out.


    </string>

    <string name="lamb_stew_with_white_radish">
Lamb stew with white radish
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 71 kcal
\nIngredients: 60g lamb, 30g radish
\nSeasoning: cilantro, 2g soy sauce, cooking wine, 2g salt, 2g salad oil, 2g cooking oil, 1g green onion, 1g ginger
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Wash and slice the lamb, soak in soy sauce and Shaojiang wine to taste.
\n2: Wash and peel the radish and slice it, chop the cilantro.
\n3: Use salad oil to stir-fry the onion and lamb, add the right amount of water.
\n4: Add radish, 40 minutes on medium heat, add cilantro to season with salt.


    </string>

    <string name="braised_lamb">
Braised Lamb
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 156 kcal
\nIngredients: 80g lamb
\nSeasoning: yellow wine, 5g green garlic, 2g ginger, 2g garlic, 2g salt, 3g rock sugar, 1g dark soy sauce, 3g fresh soy sauce, chili pepper, star anise, cinnamon, 2g red dates
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: The refrigerator lamb thawed well, let go of the water blanching, fish out.
\n2: Put the lamb into the pot.
\n3: Put down ginger, garlic, chili, star anise, cinnamon, red dates.
\n4: Pour in 500 grams of rice wine.
\n5: High heat boil.
\n6: Put in the rock sugar.
\n7: Add the right amount of soy sauce, fresh smoke, high heat boil, low heat slow stew 80 minutes.
\n8: Add the right amount of salt, cook for 5 minutes.
\n9: Put some minced green garlic, stir well.


    </string>

    <string name="mushrooms_mixes_in_the_hot_pot">
Mushrooms mixes in the hot pot
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 41 kcal
\nIngredients: 10g pancetta, 20g portobello mushroom, 20g shiitake mushroom, 20g apricot mushroom, 20g black fungus
\nSeasoning: 1g ginger, 2g green onion, 2g rock sugar, 2g soy sauce, cooking wine, 1g pepper, oil, 2g salt
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Prepare the raw materials.
\n2: Heat a pan, add a little oil, put the sliced pork into the stir-fry.
\n3: Will be sliced pork in the fat stir-fried out, the surface slightly charred add onions and ginger and rock sugar into the stir-fry.
\n4: Stir-fry a few times after adding the right amount of cooking wine and soy sauce.
\n5: Then add the appropriate amount of water, boil over high heat, cover and simmer for five minutes.
\n6: Put in the prepared mushrooms and black fungus.
\n7: Cover and continue to stew for five minutes.
\n8: Remove the lid, add salt and pepper to taste, high heat to reduce the juice can be served on a plate, the surface sprinkled with small minced onion.


    </string>

    <string name="stewed_chicken_with_mushrooms">
Stewed Chicken with Mushrooms
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 89 kcal
\nIngredients: 70g chicken
\nSeasoning: 1g ginger, 2g salt, 3g soy sauce, 20g shiitake mushrooms, 1g oil, cornstarch, 3g sugar
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Prepare the ingredients, cut the chicken into small pieces, soak the shiitake mushrooms and cut into julienne strips, cut the ginger pieces into julienne strips.
\n2: Oil, salt, cornstarch, soy sauce, sugar mix in.
\n3: Mix well and marinate for 20-30 minutes.
\n4: Put a steamer in the pot, put the marinated mushroom chicken into the pot and steam for 15 minutes on high heat.
\n5: You can also add a little chili with personal taste, the taste is better.

    </string>

    <string name="braised_chicken">
Braised chicken
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 120 kcal
\nIngredients: 70g chicken
\nSeasoning: ginger, cooking wine, 1g five spice powder, 2g soy sauce, oyster sauce, asparagus, 10g dried shiitake mushrooms, fungus, 5g green pepper, 5g red pepper, 2g shallot, dried red pepper, garlic, 2g salt, 2g rock sugar, 1g soy sauce, cooking oil
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Shiitake mushrooms soaked in advance.
\n2: Wood ear soaked in advance.
\n3: Asparagus cut into pieces, washed and soaked in water to remove the astringent taste.
\n4: Chicken chopped into walnut pieces, soaked in water in advance, changing water several times in between, until the water is clear.
\n5: Soaked chicken with sterilized tea towels or kitchen paper to absorb moisture.
\n6: Add 5 or 6 slices of ginger, 1 tbsp of cooking wine, 1 tsp of five spice powder, 1/2 tsp of salt, 1 tbsp of soy sauce, 1 tbsp of oyster sauce and grasp well, marinate for more than 20 minutes。
\n7: Drain the asparagus and set aside; cut the mushrooms into coarse shreds and set aside; wash and tear the fungus into small pieces and set aside; cut the scallions diagonally and set aside; cut the garlic into minced pieces and set aside; scrub the dried red chili peppers and set aside; if you add green and red chili peppers, you should also prepare them at this time; clarify the water of soaking mushrooms and set aside.
\n8: Boil the water with mushrooms or heat it in microwave oven until it is close to boiling, set aside.
\n9: Oil in a pan, hot pan cool oil low heat, add chicken pieces and all the marinade, slowly stir-fry until the chicken is oily, the surface is golden brown, set aside.
\n10: Stir-fry minced garlic and dried red pepper, until the pepper is dark date red.
\n11: Add the fungus, mushrooms, bamboo shoots, turn the heat to high, stir-fry evenly.
\n12: Add the chicken, stir-fry evenly over high heat.
\n13: Add rock sugar and soy sauce, stir-fry evenly.
\n14: Add the heated mushroom water, not over the chicken; if the mushroom water is not enough, add more boiling water; boil over high heat, turn down the heat, cover the pot and simmer until the chicken is cooked, checking and stirring in between.
\n15: Add salt to taste, and turn the heat to high to reduce the juice.
\n16: Until the soup thickens, add the scallions and green and red peppers, stir-fry evenly.


    </string>

    <string name="coke_chicken_wings">
Coke Chicken Wings
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 134 kcal
\nIngredients: 90g chicken wings, 50g cola
\nSeasoning: ginger, onion, garlic, 2g sugar, 2g soy sauce, 2g cooking wine, 2g chicken seasoning, 2g salt
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Prepare the chicken wings, wash them well and cut them with a knife three times. Marinate the chicken wings with soy sauce, salt, sesame oil and cooking wine for about 30 minutes.
\n2: Pour olive oil into the pot, add the chicken wings, add the right amount of ginger, and fry the chicken wings until they turn brown.
\n3: After the chicken wings are fried until browned, pour in the prepared garlic, ginger, chili, stir-fry both sides golden brown aroma flow into the gravy can be.
\n4: After pouring in the auxiliary ingredients, stir-fry a few times, then you can pour in the cola. Add two spoons of soy sauce, a spoonful of oil, a little salt, be careful, do not pour too much cola, just cover the chicken wings can be.
\n5: Simmer on high heat for 10 minutes to thicken the sauce, sprinkle with sesame seeds and serve.

    </string>

    <string name="pickle_chicken_legs">
Pickle chicken legs
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 191 kcal
\nIngredients: Chicken feet 90g
\nSeasoning: lemon 2g, onion 2g, celery, wild pepper 2g, fresh pepper 2g, cinnamon, star anise, pepper, garlic 1g, ginger 1g
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Slice the lemon and slice the onion.
\n2: Ginger, garlic patted, pepper, cinnamon, star anise washed and dried, wild mountain pepper cut, put in a container.
\n3: Phoenix claw washed, boiled in water until the chicken claw is softer, deboned, cooked and taken out, washed with water to remove the floating end, cut into two to three pieces and dried.
\n4: Drying phoenix claw into the altar, the lemon, onion, celery cover it.
\n5: Serve the boiling water in a large bowl and add garlic, pickled red pepper, wild mountain pepper, ginger and pepper after cooling.
\n6: Take the old kimchi water, pour into the water.
\n7: Dry the phoenix claw, put the lemon, onion and celery together in a large glass bowl and soak for more than 30 minutes.


    </string>

    <string name="three_cups_chicken">
Three Cups Chicken
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 175 kcal
\nIngredients: 85g chicken wings
\nSeasoning: 5g basil, 2g green onion, ginger, garlic, 1g red dry pepper, 1g red chili pepper, 2g sesame oil, rice wine, 1g soy sauce, 1g dark soy sauce, 2g sugar
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Cut the green onion into sections, ginger and garlic slices, cut the red dry pepper into sections, and cut the red pepper into small pieces. Wash the basil and remove the old stems, leaving the young leaves. Drain the liquid from the rice wine and remove the rice grains.
\n2: Heat a wok, and burst the onion, ginger, garlic and dried red pepper.
\n3: Add the cleaned chicken wings and stir-fry for a while. Add the other seasonings and bring to a boil over high heat, turn to medium-low heat and simmer for about 20 minutes.
\n4: Finally wait for the cooked juice to thicken over high heat, then add the basil leaves.


    </string>

    <string name="lettuce_with_oyster_sauce">
Lettuce with Oyster Sauce
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 30 kcal
\nIngredients: 90g lettuce
\nSeasoning: 5g oyster sauce, 3g soy sauce, 2g garlic, 1g green onion, corn starch
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Lettuce break off the leaves, rinse well and set aside.
\n2: Chop the green onion and garlic, 2 tablespoons of oyster sauce, 1 tablespoon of soy sauce, 1 tablespoon of starch, add water to make oyster sauce.
\n3: Lettuce into the boiling water, a little sugar in the water.
\n4: Hot cooked lettuce drained on a plate.
\n5: Hot pot with oil, burnt onion and garlic and then pour the seasoned oyster sauce.
\n6: Simmer slowly over low heat until thickened.
\n7: Boil the oyster sauce off the heat, drizzle on the lettuce can be.


    </string>


    <string name="steamed_chinese_cabbage_in_supreme_soup">
Steamed Chinese Cabbage in Supreme Soup
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 20 kcal
\nIngredients: 95g cabbage, chicken, ham, pork ribs, dried scallops, chicken breast, whole lean pork
\nSeasoning: 3g salt, cooking wine, 2g green onion, ginger, water
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: First boil the water broth. Put the old hen into a large soup pot, add water, ginger and green onion, bring to a boil, add wine and simmer for 3 hours.
\n2: At the same time the chicken breast and lean pork chopped into paste, respectively, add an appropriate amount of water to mix into a porridge for use.
\n3: After the soup has simmered for 3 hours, use a sieve to separate out all the soup dregs and floating oil. Pour the broth into another pot, boil, add the pork paste and stir well, turn to medium-low heat, wait for it to slowly spread, meat paste float, use a small spoon to fish out the meat paste; then bring the soup to boil again, the chicken paste in 2 times, according to the same treatment of pork paste; finally, the broth is thoroughly separated from the dregs, remove the oil, to be fresh and clear as water, salt to taste, to be used.
\n4: Divide the soup into two pots. Select the tender cabbage hearts, put them into one of the pots of broth, sear them until they are seventy years old, rinse them in clear water to cool them, pierce them repeatedly with a fine silver needle, put them in a colander and drizzle them down with the original broth from above until they are hot.
\n5: Put the cabbage heart on the bottom of the bowl, boil another pot of broth and ladle into the bowl.


    </string>


    <string name="stir_fried_pea_shoots_with_garlic">
Stir-Fried Pea Shoots with Garlic
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 24 kcal
\nIngredients: 95g beansprouts
\nSeasoning: 3g garlic, oil, 2g salt
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Bean seedlings wash clean.
\n2: Hot pan with oil and pour garlic.
\n3: Stir-fry garlic and then pour in the beansprouts. Quickly stir-fry.
\n4: Bean seedlings browned salt, continue to stir-fry quickly, all browned.



    </string>


    <string name="vinegar_pepper_shredded_potatoes">
Vinegar-pepper shredded potatoes
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 120 kcal
\nIngredients: 90g potatoes
\nSeasoning: 5g chili, white vinegar, 1g green onion, oil, 2g salt, 2g chicken seasoning
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Peel potatoes and cut into shreds.
\n2: Put the shredded potatoes into cool water to wash off the excess starch.
\n3: Dried chili pepper cut into small pieces, garlic patted.
\n4: Add water to the pot, bring to a boil, put in the potatoes shredded hot for half a minute, take out and rinse with cold water, drain the water.
\n5: The pot of oil, the pepper frying on low heat, fish out the pepper.
\n6: Pour into the dried chili and garlic explosive pot over high heat and sauté.
\n7: Pour into the shredded potatoes, stir-fry quickly and quickly.
\n8: Pour in white vinegar along the side of the pot, vinegar evaporates when it meets heat, leaving vinegar aroma. Add salt and sugar to taste.
\n9: The whole process of high heat stir-fry quickly, to ensure that the potatoes crisp. Add small onion before serving.


    </string>


    <string name="sponge_gourd_with_eggs">
Sponge Gourd with Eggs
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 99 kcal
\nIngredients: 60g loofah, 35g egg
\nSeasoning: oil, 3g salt, 2g garlic
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Loofah peeled and sliced, eggs with salt beaten into an egg mixture, garlic chopped.
\n2: Heat oil in a pan and pour in the egg mixture.
\n3: When it starts to solidify a little, use chopsticks to quickly scatter.
\n4: Pull the egg to the side, add the oil and pop the minced garlic.
\n5: Add the loofah.
\n6: Stir-fry until the loofah changes color and water, put salt and stir-fry well.


    </string>


    <string name="grilled_fresh_squid">
Grille fresh squid
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 92 kcal
\nIngredients: 80g squid
\nSeasoning: 10g onion, 5g chili, 1g cumin, 2g sesame, 1g salt, 1g pepper
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Squid clean, cut, onion cut shred.
\n2: Heat the oil in the pot, stir-fry the squid until all the water is gone.
\n3: Add chili noodles, cumin, sesame seeds, salt, pepper noodles, continue to stir-fry.
\n4: Add a little sweet noodle sauce with soy sauce and stir well.
\n5: Put the iron plate hot, brush a small amount of oil, immediately add such as a small amount of onion, and finally put in the squid.



    </string>


    <string name="braised_sea_cucumber_with_scallion">
Braised Sea Cucumber With Scallion
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 110 kcal
\nIngredients: 70g sea cucumber, 20g broccoli
\nSeasoning: 2g yellow onion, 1g canola oil, 2g oyster sauce, 2g soy sauce, 2g salt, 1g pepper
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Often the dried wild sea cucumbers in cool water, put them into a pot of cool water and cook slowly for about twenty minutes, remove the guts and wash them, cook them repeatedly in cool water until they can be pinched through, then put them into cool water with ice cubes and refrigerate them for three days.
\n2: Cut into long strips.
\n3: Prepare broccoli and yellow onion. Wash the broccoli and cut the yellow onion.
\n4: Blanch the broccoli in boiling water with oil and salt, drain and place on a large plate.
\n5: Heat oil on low heat, fry onion until the skin turns dark and take out.
\n6: Add water, put sea cucumber, oyster sauce, soy sauce, pepper.
\n7: Medium heat for about five minutes.
\n8: Large fire will be the soup collection.

    </string>


    <string name="steamed_scallop_with_garlic_and_vermicelli">
Steamed Scallop With Garlic And Vermicelli
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 127 kcal
\nIngredients: 60g scallops, 30g vermicelli
\nSeasoning: 5g garlic, 1g scallion, 1g ginger, dried chili pepper, 1g salt, 1g steamed fish soy sauce, 1g sugar
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: Vermicelli softened with cold water. Chop the onion, ginger, garlic and dried chili and set aside. Wash the scallops, remove the mud and intestines, scallop shells brush clean.
\n2: Put some oil in the pot, stir-fry onion ginger garlic, put salt, soy sauce, sugar, soup, high heat to dry soup.
\n3: Scallop shells put on the vermicelli.
\n4: Each scallop in turn put: fan, garlic, scallop meat.
\n5: Put garlic on the top of the scallop meat. Put a small piece of ginger in the pot and steam for about 8 minutes.


    </string>


    <string name="buddha_jumps_over_the_wall">
Buddha Jumps Over The Wall
\n
\n
\nPer 100g - calories: 175 kcal
\nIngredients:  10g skate sharks fin, 10g baby abalone, 10g scallop, 10g shrimp, 10g quail egg, 10g sliced asparagus, 10g shiitake mushroom, 10g cooked chicken, 10g pork belly
\nSeasoning: 1g ginger, 1g Shaoxing Hua Diao wine, 6g stock, 1g salt, 1g white pepper
\n
\nSteps:
\n1: First lay the ginger slices on the bottom of the jar.
\n2: Then lay the asparagus slices.
\n3: Lay the mushrooms in turn.
\n4: Then add the cooked chicken.
\n5: At the same time, put in the shrimp.
\n6: Put in the scallop.
\n7: Then put in quail eggs.
\n8: Then put in the pork belly.
\n9: Lay the shark fins and spread them flat.
\n10: put a small abalone on the top.
\n11: Spoon half of the Hua Diao wine into the jar.
\n12: Fry the ladle on the fire and fill with the stock.
\n13: Pour in the other half of the Hua Diao wine and bring to a boil.
\n14: Season with a pinch of salt.
\n15: Then sprinkle in a little pepper.
\n16: Ladle the soup into the jar.
\n17: Cover the jar with a lid.
\n18: Wrap the jar with plastic wrap.
\n19: To seal the jar more tightly.
\n20: Put the sealed jars into the cage.
\n21: Cover the pot and steam for two hours on medium heat.
\n22: After steaming, remove and cut the plastic wrap with scissors.
\n23: Place a plate under the jar and serve.



    </string>


</resources>